RAGHUNATH DHUNGANA

Career Objective

To obtain a challenging career that demands individual responsibilities and cooperative team effort. To become a full-fledged professional in an IT Industry where I can use my technical and networking skills, which contribute the growth of the company and myself. Technology shouldn't be more difficult to the users. So, I would want to work in creating and engineering technology, namely computing resources. Relaying and presenting information and products to the public would be of great interest to me.

Professional Experience

April 2021 - Till Date

• IT Supervisor • The Arts Club - Dubai, United Arab Emirates

September 2017 - April 2021

• IT Support Supervisor • Millennium Hotel Group - Kurdistan, Iraq

February 2017 - September 2017

• IT Specialist • Emaar Hospitality Group - Dubai, UAE

March 2016 - September 2016

IT System Admin • Shangri-La Hotel – Abu Dhabi, UAE

October 2013 – February 2016

• IT System Technician • Radisson Blu Hotel – Doha, Qatar

September 2008 - September 2013

• IT System Admin • Compro Technology – Kathmandu, Nepal

Duties and Responsibilities

- All IT Systems are running smoothly in the organization and the IT function is acting in a proactive manner rather than reactive.
- Manage daily operations of the IT department.
- IT is driving efficiencies in the use of applications enabling the other departments to successfully complete their tasks.
- All Corporate IT related policies and procedures have been implemented and a successful self-audit has been carried out.
- Develop new strategies and IT procedures to increase efficiency, enhance workflow and improve guest satisfaction
- Solve technical and operational challenges in the scope of IT reported by users.
- To assist the IT Manager in all stages of the day-to-day operation of the Hotel.
- To support computers in hardware and software malfunction in coordination with all the departments.
- Assess infrastructure on regular basis to ensure it continues to meet necessary demands.
- Coordinate the needs of in-house IT experts and remote employees, vendors and contractors.
- Maintain complete record of the systems related inventory.
- Plans, designs, and implements and administer user networks for an organization.
- To manage and prioritize any IT problems, impacting either revenue and/or the guest for quick resolution and pro-actively seek for preventative maintenance.
- Perform all duties and responsibilities in a timely and efficient manner in accordance with established company policies.



Contact

- P.O.B 506741, Dubai, United Arab Emirates
- +971-561962437
- dhunganar@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/raghudhungana
- aryan.dhu (Raghu Dhungana)

.

.

Work Summary

Strong experience in IT System support & networking with proven origination skills and ability to lead cross-functional project.

Constantly striving for efficiency and effectiveness in job function, able to work well independently, as well as a part of team with great interpersonal skills

Strong Area on Technology

• Clint OS:

Windows 98, 2000, 2003 XP, Vista, 7, 8 and Windows 10 and 11)

• Server OS:

NT Server, windows 2000,2003,2008, 2012 & 2016, Server 2019)

• **M.S. Office** (Office 7,10,13,16, 19 and office 365)

Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

Graphic Designing:

Adobe Photoshop and PageMaker

• Technical Support:

Troubleshooting problems pertaining to Performance Tuning, Network Administration, Application Conflicts and system Bugs. Supporting field staff on technical details, support issues & leased circuits etc.

• Security:

Policy to protect internal network against unauthorized access, and to make provisions for disaster recovery in the event of successful intrusion/attack Maintaining and configuring Norton/Symantec Antivirus enterprise edition.

Diploma in Hardware and Networking

Fundamentals of Computer & Electronics

Operating Systems

Installation of Hardware and Software

Computer Assembly & Maintenance

Preventive Maintenance & Trouble Shooting

Anti-Virus Overview & Configuration and installation

Concepts of Network

Components, Protocols, Cabling and Wi-Fi

LAN Setup, Peer to Peer and switch based

DNS, DHCP, Active Directory Doman Services (DA-DS)

Windows 2008/12/16 User Management & Security

Windows File System Security

Live working Experience with Hospitality Application

- Opera Hotel Edition (PMS system for Front Office & Sales)
- Micros 9700 / Simphony (POS System for Restaurants and Bars)
- Tiger TMS ComTelco (Telephone Call Accounting System)
- Oasys / Bayan payroll System (Human Recourse & General Cashier)
- fidelio material control (FMC) purchasing, Inventory Management
- Visitor (Card Scanning System for Bars and Night Club)
- SAFLOK + Interal System (Guest Room key card system)
- IFC 8 (Interface system for opera, micros POS, TMS, SAFLOK & 3C)
- Symantec Backup Exec (Backup system for opera and Data)
- Samsotech Vicas (Passport scanning system Front / back office)

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet

• • • • • •

.

- MacAfee Antivirus Antivirus Server and Security
- AntLabs Internet hotspot system
- Connected Guest Internet Management & Billing System
- Locatel IP TV System (IP TV System for Rooms)

Training Summary

- Microsoft Office (word, Excel, Power Point, E-mail) Kathmandu, Nepal
- Diploma in Hardware & Networking Kathmandu, Nepal
- Yes I Can! (Delivering the promise programme) Radisson Blu hotel, Doha
- Fire safety training Radisson Blu hotel, Doha, Qatar
- General fire prevention & The use of Fire Extinguishers
- Shangri-La Care 1 & 2 programme Shangei-La hotel, Abu Dhabi

Education

- Bachelor in Business Study (B.B.S) T.U Board
- Intermediate in Commerce (I. Com) T.U Board
- School Leaving Certificate (S.L.C) HMG Board

Personal Details

Current Address : ICD Brokfild Plae DIFC, Dubai, UAE

Permanent Address : Sankhu, Kathmandu, Nepal

Contact No. :+971-561962437 Email : dhunganar@gmail.com

Nationality : Nepalese Civil Status : Married

Language Known : English, Nepalese and Hindi

Gender : Male

Date of Birth : 22nd March 1987

P.P Number : 06551659 (Issued from Kathmandu, Nepal)

• • • • • • •

.

Reference

Will be furnished upon request